Whoa!
I like it! Like a photo almost
it's very,
Yeah... Brilliant
Doing a small painting...
a small canvas, it’s really hard, but I like it
Yeah, I like the balance
I found between, you know, detail,
but not too much
Baby..!
it flew inside?
And he hurts...
did it hurt?
Yeah, I think it's over.
Oh my God.
I just opened the door.
Just open the door?
Baby,
maybe just scared
Are you fine?
Oh, no.
I'm afraid she's finished.
maybe she's just scared.
Do you think she, just, like,
bump in something?
I opened the door, flew inside.
I think she hit the window.
to fly outside again
because she goes to the light.
But, Yeah.
She's gone, babe
Maybe not
Maybe she’s just scared,
I'll stay with her.
I don't care about the painting anymore.
baby! she’s fine
everything is ok
you can fly away if you want.
Oh, no!
In the house again!
but go careful
Otherwise,
open the skylight first,
because you gonna fly out against the window
She likes it here.
Oh that’s good.
Oh, yeah, you see?
See you, like, a little bit..
she’s fine
And also young.
Good.
Ciao!
so much snow here!
You guys were here...
I mean, a while ago, I think. Yeah.
I was building the stove, or something
Or just before
The, the border behind your bed...
but then the concrete part. Really?
Yeah, I think so.
There was.
I thought it was a concrete floor already
Or dirt ?
No, the concrete floor was already there
But I remember looking up
and it was really high. Oh the floor was not in there
OK, so it was November 24th or something.
so you hold your scraper to it
To flatten it
I got from the middle outwards a few times
to flatten it
slowly, and then you see the, the lines.
Yeah.
And there's a bit of white dust
from my studio, but,
it's fine. If you wash it
then it’s gone
And here?
I think, those are the cream
the shallow bowls
for shallow food
thank you so much.
You're welcome. it’s beautiful
And in the same, and after it
I think there were like wolf...
or dog, I don't know,
but I think we'll be... Lady...
Yeah. But there were bigger than Lady
or Lady
because it's not Lady, it was really big
You need to check the
the nails.
How it works?
Because the dogs,
they predominantly... they go,
like, unless it's wild dogs,
because then have similar nails as the wolfs
But if it's like a normal dog,
which would go with...
with a normal person
and then would drift off a bit.
The nails would be kind of stump
Whereas the nails of the wolf and the wild dogs
They're more sharp.
But this is a sign
which is not that much reliable
But mostly with the wolves
you will find the shape in their prints.
You have the... I have to show you later
Let’s say...
if this is the... you want some of this?
Two fingers
Like, these are the fingers of the wolves,
and if you go between the first
and the second finger, you could reach
the other side of the stamp of the hand
Without a barrier
So you really get
the X shape, whereas when you
When it would be a dog, it would go
like this and then it would go down.
So it would be more like, an H.
All right.
So these are some marks...
and then wolf prints...
They are really big, but then, there’s big dog prints as well
But Natalya was saying that she was convinced that there might be a lynch.
Okay. Yeah.
She said that. Something she talks a lot about
But then, I mean, I haven't seen her,
but it’s probable
I mean, the area of the lynch is very big
You know, an enourmous hunting ground, so
The other side is finished
OK, so you have the final...
Yeah. The last triangles...
I’m mortaring those in
Okay, for a bit more stability.
It looks really good!
On top of that is, like this
kind of width, cut from “lose”
and  they're sitting on top
also with cement
and that's it.
the other option would be
the triangle concrete top, right
But I'm going for the flatter one. oh no, no, you you
you should go...
for the traditional way,
considering the other houses.
Yeah.
But from a distance
it looks very different.
It does..? if you would stand there
you know, the color
I mean the color will probably
over time it,
it will blend in more with the color.
But the shapes
will be always a bit...
But it does look great
Yeah, I'm happy with it.
Yeah.
It's also the dust, like,  from cutting the,
the silica is very white,
so that's why the roof is very white.
Oh yeah.
that will wash off
tomorrow if the rain ... tonight yes
Yeah.
I thought it was going to be snow, but...
Oh snow?
No I like two days ago
it looked like snow.
But now it looks like two degrees warmer,
so it's probably will be rain
We'll see.
There's still plenty up there. Coming over,
I just said....
The birds are back singing
And so I went for a walk, and,
then I heard you hammering or,
I don’t know, drilling or something.
Yeah,
yeah, I know it's still a little winter.
And if you look up, it still looks pretty....
There’s a lot of snow up there, yea
OK, the roof is water tight, which is great.
I can see it on the
the bitumen, on the edges,
underneath the stones,
if that is wet, water comes through.
And I thought there was a one spot
over there, but I looked with a light.
It doesn't go in.
It was just from the edge, dripping on
Where it was sticking out, so it's all good.
This is moderate rain.
It's not going very hard.
But, Yeah, I know, I'm comfident
It's fine.
There's enough waterproof layers to keep,
keep the rain out.
So good news.
The mortar is still a bit too soft
Too brush it clean
And that's
because of the cold temperatures.
So it cures quite slowly
The lime mortar, with a little bit of cement,
to have a bit more strength
and rigidity
because it gets a lot of rainwater.
Obviously.
I wanted to finish it, but
tonight is probably going to snow a bit.
Or at least it's going to be cold,
maybe just below zero.
And this needs one more layer of stone.
And I didn't want to do fresh mortar,
because it's too cold.
It won’t cure well
so that has to be done next week
bits of stain here
and there at the ends of the rafters.
The boards need to go on, I started preparing them
they go on the outside here.
I might put them on when the
scaffolding is down, it’s a bit easier
and then the roof will be finished.
Yeah.
200 episodes.
This series is, now...
It's kind of crazy to think about it,
a small film every week
I really enjoy still doing it.
So I'm just going to keep going.
I appreciate you being here.
I enjoy reading the comments on Sunday,
Monday and Tuesday usually,
Yeah.
It's such a strange thing this YouTube.
So many people seeing,
looking at your life every day.
I'm... we’re used to it.
Ela too now. She's been here
for, more than a year or so
And we enjoy it a lot.
Reading your comments, ideas,
stories, memories...
tips and tricks.
It's a great thing. So,
next week will be here again.